PAUL NITSCHE

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

A dedicated professional with experience working in different industries and employees at all levels of an organization. Dependable and goal-oriented individual accustomed to a strong work ethic and adapting to changing priorities. Excellent communicator with a record of accomplishments both from a scholastic and employment perspective.

CORE COMPETENCIES

Program Development • Employee Management • Business Computing • Budget Management •
Strategic Planning • Operations Management • Data Wrangling • Exceptional Organizational and Time-Management Skills • Microsoft Office Platform • Computational Thinking • Database Management

EDUCATION

University of Iowa, Iowa City, IA

Bachelor of Science, Business Analytics and Information Systems Anticipated Graduation: December 2024 (GPA in Major: 3.00/4.00)

EXPERIENCE

House Painter, Kraven Expert Painting and Wall Hanging, Chicago, IL

May 2022 - Present

- Prepare surfaces for painting, including sanding, patching, and priming
- Apply paint, varnish, and other finishes to walls, ceilings, and other surfaces
- Use a variety of tools and equipment, such as brushes, rollers, and spray guns and ensure all safety protocols are followed
- Keep accurate records of materials used and time spent on each job and report to management
- Work with other tradespeople to ensure a successful project; train new painters through effective communication and learned technical skills

Chef, Fox's Restaurant, Chicago IL

March 2021 - April 2022

- Set up workstations with all needed ingredients and cooking equipment
- Prepared ingredients to use in cooking (chopping and peeling vegetables, cutting meat etc.)
- Cooked food in various utensils or grillers and check food while cooking to stir or turn
- Ensured great presentation by dressing dishes before they are served
- Kept a sanitized and orderly environment in the kitchen

Barback, Open Outcry, Chicago, IL

June 2020 – December 2020

- Prepared garnishes, refill ice wells, change beer kegs and restock napkins and straws
- Kept the bar stocked with liquor, syrups, glasses, napkins and all other necessary items before and during service hours
- Coordinated with managers, kitchen staff and security personnel to ensure efficient service
- Handled emergency situations, such as cleaning up broken glasses and clearing up clogged drains
- Promptly addressed any customer service issues and referred to management when necessary

ACTIVITIES

- Maeve McNicholas Pediatric Cancer Foundation Committee Member
- University of Iowa Volleyball Intramurals Member
- Marist High School Peer Leadership Program Member

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST